http://www.ebbets.com/pages/privacy

$5 Flat rate shipping | Free on orders $125 and up*
0
Rewards
Account
My Cart: (0)
Privacy
AT EBBETS.COM YOUR PRIVACY IS VERY IMPORTANT TO US.We do not sell, share, rent or trade your electronically provided personal information to others. We understand your concerns about online security and privacy. Here at Ebbets Field Flannels our goal is to ensure that your personal and payment information remains secure and your privacy is protected.
PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy applies to information Ebbets Field Flannels learns about or obtains from you when you visit the Site, and does not apply to any other website, whether or not it is affiliated with or linked to this Site. Definitions contained in the Site's Terms also apply to this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated in and made a part of the Terms. Your access or use of the Site constitutes your legally binding acceptance of and agreement to this Privacy Policy.
The provisions of this Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time in Ebbets Field Flannels' sole discretion and as provided by applicable law. Ebbets Field Flannels will attempt to provide advance notice by posting such changes to the Site at least thirty (30) days prior to implementation, or a shorter period as required by applicable law and/or business conditions. You should check this Privacy Policy frequently for any such changes, but in any case your continued access or use of the Site will constitute acceptance of any modifications. You may "opt-out" of any change as provided below. Ebbets Field Flannels' use of information gathered or obtained at any time is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such use.
The Site is not directed at children, and Ebbets Field Flannels will not knowingly collect any personal information from any person under age 13. Ebbets Field Flannels complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and does not knowingly permit submission of Personal Information by anyone under 13 years of age. You must be over age 13 to use the Site.
CONTROLLER OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONAny personal information provided to, or collected by Ebbets Field Flannels through the Site is controlled by Ebbets Field Flannels.
WHAT WE COLLECTYou may review information collected about you via the Site, and delete or modify personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address or home address or telephone number ("Personal Information") by following our Correct/Update Procedure. This does not apply to information collected by cookies and used internally to recognize you and/or facilitate your visits to the Site, or information we may retain to comply with legal requirements.
We do not sell, share, rent or trade your electronically provided personal information to others. We understand your concerns about online security and privacy. Here at Ebbets Field Flannels our goal is to ensure that your personal and payment information remains secure and your privacy is protected.
To better serve you, we utilize the Pinterest Tag to track the items you view.
